{
    "subject": "resource/11:14",
    "predicate": "property/director",
    "object": "resource/Greg_Marcks",
    "human_readable": "The director of '11:14' is Greg Marcks.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.876821756362915,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Greg Marcks and the movie '11:14'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8752114176750183,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Greg Marcks."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8038681745529175,
            "question": "Who directed the film '11:14'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6014288663864136,
            "question": "What is Greg Marcks known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5985884070396423,
            "question": "Has Greg Marcks won any awards for his directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5000516772270203,
            "question": "What other films has Greg Marcks worked on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49030208587646484,
            "question": "What genre is likely associated with the film '11:14' based on its director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3254677951335907,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about the plot of '11:14'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31934404373168945,
            "question": "What year was the film '11:14' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24544881284236908,
            "question": "Is there a specific theme explored in '11:14'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of '11:14' is Greg Marcks.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1680_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film '11:14' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1680_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more details about the plot of '11:14'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1680_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is likely associated with the film '11:14' based on its director?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1680_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1680_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1680_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1680_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1680_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1680_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1680_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1680_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1680_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1680_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1680_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"11:14\" is a film directed by Greg Marcks, thus supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}